Either the thrashing or the interview, the
o la culerada o la entrevista la junta
power meeting that was thought to be a
de poder que se pensaba
good match, great atmosphere, we said
bueno partidazo ambientazo hemos
goodbye to Mascherano, we
despedido a mascherano hemos dado la
welcomed
bienvenida
Coutinho, who was good in the middle,
a coutinho que el bueno de media estaba
every time he touched it
cada vez que la tocaba
here in the stadium the emotions are
aquí en el estadio las emociones se
magnified,
magnifican
I defended Coutinho's arrival, it
he defendido a la llegada de coutinho
felt electric when the
sintió eléctrico cuando cuando llega el
end of the match came, well, Suárez and the
final del partido pues suárez y el show
Mateu Lahoz show, which won't be a yellow card,
de mateu lahoz que no será amarilla
where the thousand tickets, that's why
donde los mil entradas por eso ya
we were already counting on it, and nothing remains, a match more
contábamos y nada queda un partido más
difficult than it could have seemed, to
difícil de lo que podía parecer que
come back from 1-0, a very tough result,
remontar un 1-0 un resultado muy chungo
I hope we have learned for
espero que hayamos aprendido de cara el
Chelsea, we can no longer go there and lose 10,
chelsea ya no podemos ir allí perder 10
choose for you, who dies, which seems like a, it
elijan por ti
could be the
que muere que parece un puede ser la
idea, night, 80,000 people who were shouting,
idea noche 80.000 personas que gritando
God, I was going to go, I love it, he tried the
dios iba a ir le encante probó mejor la
voice better, to sleep,
voz a dormir
milk with honey,
leche con miel
we have process cooks,
tenemos a cocineros de proceso
the best in the universe
lo mejor del universo
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
we are going to see, never ever in our lives,
vamos a ver nunca nunca en nuestra vida
all of us who are here are
todos los que estamos aquí somos
initiates, we
iniciados
will have to wait
habrá que esperar
[Laughter]
[Risas]
Valverde,
valverde
yesterday we passed like others who
ayer hemos pasado como otros que
continue wanting to win and winning  Barça Barça
seguimos queriendo ganar y ganando barça